Class of 1977 Records, 1973-[ongoing]
Smith College Archives
Class of 1977 Records
1973-[ongoing]
Smith College. Class of 1977.
RG 80 UUID:f619efbe-1800-444f-a0e6-36f1db47066d
5 boxes (1.9 linear ft.)
Smith College Archives Northampton, MA
This collection contains photographs, invitations, songs, newspaper clippings, and other memorabilia from the commencement and reunions of the Class of 1977.
The Class of 1977 was the ninety-ninth graduating class of Smith College.
The Class of 1977 Records contain materials describing the history and activities of the Class of 1977, including materials from commencement, reunions, and other important events. Types of materials include photographs, invitations, songs, newspaper clippings, programs, letters, and other memorabilia.
Individual biographical files are also available, and often include photographs, photo albums, newspaper clippings, letters and correspondences, and class notes.
Information on Use
Terms of Access and Use
The records are open for research according to the regulations of the Smith College Archives without any additional restrictions.
History of the Collection
The Class of 1977 Records were created by the students and donated to the College Archives.
- Alumnae Directory 1977 (Box 2267, Folder 1)
- Commencement 1977 (Box 2267, Folder 2)
- Commencement Photographs 1977 (Box 2267, Folder 3)
- Commencement Speaker 1977 (Box 2267, Folder 4)
- Freshman Handbook 1973-1974 (Box 2267, Folder 5)
- Groups 1973-1977 (Box 2267, Folder 6)
- Last Chapel 1977 (Box 2267, Folder 7)
- Class Letters 1997-2002 (Box 2267, Folder 8)
- Class List 1974 (Box 2267, Folder 9)
- Reunion 1979-1982 (Box 2267, Folder 10)
- Yearbook Photographs 1977 (Box 2267, Folder 11)
- Yearbook-Senior Photographs 1977 (Box 2267, Folder 12)
- Reunion Book 2002 (Box 2267.1, Folder 1)
- Yearbook-Freshman Photographs 1974 (Box 2267.1, Folder 2)
- Yearbook-Freshman Photographs 1974 (Box 2267.1, Folder 3)